<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<subjects>
  <subject>
    <subjectName>CompTIA A+ 1101</subjectName>
    <Topics>
      <topicName>Mobile Devices</topicName>
      <subTopics>
        <subTopicName>Laptop component installation</subTopicName>
        <questions>
          <question>What types of batteries do laptop computers use?</question>
          <answer>NiCad or NiMH or Lithium Ion (best and prevalent today)</answer>
          <question>What types of RAM do laptop computers use?</question>
          <answer>Dual Data Rate Synchronized Dynamic Random Access Memory</answer>
          <question>What types of DDR do laptop computers use?</question>
          <answer>DDR3 or DDR4 or DDR5</answer>
          <question>What is a dual channel DDR?</question>
          <answer>Dual channel DDRs get double speed by pairing up. They must be installed in pairs.</answer>
          <question>Tell me about DDR3</question>
          <answer>DDR3 has an 8-bit buffer allowing it to run at twice system clock speed. It has either 240 or 204 pins (so).</answer>
          <question>Tell me about DDR4</question>
          <answer>DDR4 can run at eight times system clock speed. It has either 288 or 260 pins (so).</answer>
          <question>Tell me about DDR5</question>
          <answer>DDR5 can also run at eight times system clock speed. It has either 288 or 262 pins (s0).</answer>
        </questions>
        <subTopicName>Mobile Displays</subTopicName>
        <questions>
          <question>What types of displays do laptop computers use?</question>
          <answer>IPS or TN or VA or OLED</answer>
          <question>What are the strengths and weaknesses of IPS displays?</question>
          <answer>In-Plane Switching displays are inexpensive and have great color but are slow.</answer>
          <question>What are the strengths and weaknesses of TN displays?</question>
          <answer>Twisted Nematic displays are fast, but don't show well off axis.</answer>
          <question>What are the strengths and weaknesses of VA displays?</question>
          <answer>Vertical Alignment displays are medium speed and color and price.</answer>
          <question>What are the strengths and weaknesses of OLED displays?</question>
          <answer>Organic Light-Emitting Diode displays are thin, don't require a backlight, and expensive.</answer>
        </questions>
        <subTopicName>Accessories and Ports</subTopicName>
        <questions>

        </questions>
        <subTopicName>Configure connectivity</subTopicName>
        <questions>

        </questions>
      </subTopics>
    </Topics>
    <Topics>
      <topicName>Networks</topicName>
      <subTopics>
        <subTopicName></subTopicName>
      </subTopics>
    </Topics>
    <Topics>
      <topicName>Hardware</topicName>
      <subTopics>
        <subTopicName></subTopicName>
      </subTopics>
    </Topics>
    <Topics>
      <topicName>Virtualization and Cloud Computing</topicName>
      <subTopics>
        <subTopicName></subTopicName>
      </subTopics>
    </Topics>
    <Topics>
      <topicName>Troubleshooting</topicName>
      <subTopics>
        <subTopicName></subTopicName>
      </subTopics>
    </Topics>
  </subject>
  <subject>
    <subjectName>CompTIA A+ 1102</subjectName>
    <subTopics>

    </subTopics>
  </subject>
</subjects>
